Guide to the University of Pittsburgh Alumni Association Records, 1895-2012 UA.6.5.1
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Alumni Council and Board of Trustees, 1869-2007; II.
  - Alumni Council & General Meetings, 2.
    - General Alumni Association Minutes, 1914 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - 1930-1959
      - Alumni Council Executive Committee Minutes, 1933-1939 (Box 10, Folder 13)
      - Alumni Council Minutes, 1939-1946 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - 1960-1969
      - Alumni Council Executive Committee, 1961-1966 (Box 10, Folder 15)
      - Alumni Council, 1963-1965 (Box 10, Folder 16-17)
      - Alumni Council, 1965-1966 (Box 10, Folder 18)
      - Alumni Council, 1966-1967 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - 1970-1981
      - General Alumni Association, 1974-1976 (Box 10, Folder 20-21)
      - General Alumni Association, 1976-1978 (Box 10, Folder 22-24)
      - Alumni Council, 1978-1981 (Box 10, Folder 25-26)
    - 1981-1990
      - Alumni Council, 1981-1982 (Box 11, Folder 1-3)
      - Alumni Council, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 4-9)
      - Alumni Council, 1983-1984 (Box 11, Folder 10-16)
      - Alumni Council, 1984-1985 (Box 12, Folder 1)
      - Alumni Council, 1985-1986 (Box 12, Folder 2-9)
      - Alumni Council and Executive Committee Meetings, 1986-1987 (Box 12, Folder 10-12)
      - Alumni Council, 1987-1988 (Box 12, Folder 13-15)
      - Alumni Council, 1988-1989 (Box 12, Folder 16-19)
      - Alumni Council, 1989-1990 (Box 12, Folder 20-21)
      - Alumni Council, 1989-1990 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - 1990-1999
      - Alumni Association Minutes, 1990-1991 (Box 13, Folder 2-5)
      - Alumni Association Minutes, 1991-1992 (Box 13, Folder 6-11)
      - Alumni Association Minutes, 1992-1993 (Box 13, Folder 12-16)
      - Alumni Association Minutes, 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 17-21)
      - Alumni Association Minutes, 1996-1997 (Box 14, Folder 1-4)
  - Board of Directors, Trustees, & Executive Committee, 3.
    - Board of Trustees Meetings, 1992-2002 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Board of Directors, 1995-1996 (Box 14, Folder 6-10)
    - Board & Executive Committee Meetings, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 11-14)
    - Board & Executive Committee Meetings, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 15-17)
    - Board & Executive Committee Meetings, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 1-2, Folder 18)
    - Board & Executive Committee Meetings, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 3-5)
    - Board & Executive Committee Meetings, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 6-8)
    - Board & Executive Committee Meetings, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 9-12)
    - Board & Executive Committee Meetings, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 13-15)
    - Board & Executive Committee Meetings, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 1-6)
    - Board & Executive Committee Meetings, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 7-9)
    - Board & Executive Committee Meetings, 2007 (Box 16, Folder 10-11)
    - Alumni Trustees (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Career Development Committee, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Various Committees, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Various Committees, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Various Committees, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Presentation- Executive Director's Report, May 17, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Presentation- Eva Bloom to Board of Directors, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Board of Directors- Updates, 2002-2004 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Board of Directors- Updates, 2005-2006 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Board of Directors/ALC Giving, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Email Survey, 1998-1999 (Box 17, Folder 1-2, Folder 22)
  - Board Retreats & Orientations, 4.
    - Board Retreat, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Executive Committee/Blue and Gold Society Retreat, September, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Executive Committee/Blue and Gold Society Retreat, September, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - New Board Member Orientation, September 15, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - New Board Member Orientation, June 21, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - New Board Member Orientation, May 17, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - New Board Member Orientation, April 23, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - New Board Member Orientation, September 10, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Nominations Committee, 5.
    - General Alumni Association Elections Since 1965 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Elections- Alumni Officers/Directors and Trustees, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Nominations Committee (Restricted), 1995 (Box 17, Folder 13-14)
    - Nominations Committee (Restricted), 1996 (Box 17, Folder 15-16)
    - Nominations Committee (Restricted), 1997 (Box 17, Folder 17-18)
    - Nominations (Restricted), 1997-1998 (Box 17, Folder 19-21)
    - Nominations- Alumni Trustees (Restricted), 1998 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Nominations- Directors at Large (Restricted), 1998 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Nominations Meeting (Restricted), October 4, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Nominations Committee (Restricted), 1999 (Box 18, Folder 2-3)
    - Nominations (Restricted), 1999 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Nominations Committee Meeting (Restricted), January 18, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Nominations Committee Meeting (Restricted), February 5, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Nominations (Restricted), 2000 (Box 18, Folder 7-8)
    - Nominations Committee Meeting (Restricted), February 3, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Nominations (Restricted), 2001 (Box 18, Folder 10-11)
    - Nominations- Directors at Large (Restricted), 2001-2003 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Nominations Committee Meeting (Restricted), November 16, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Nominations Committee Meeting (Restricted), January 25, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Nominations Committee Meeting (Restricted), February 21, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Nominations Committee Meeting (Restricted), April 5, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Nominations Committee Meeting (Restricted), December 15, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Nominations Committee (Restricted), 2003 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Nominations- Directors at Large and Regional Directors (Restricted), 2003 (Box 18, Folder 19-20)
    - Nominations Committee Meeting (Restricted), January 15, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Nominations (Restricted), 2003 (Box 19, Folder 21-23)
    - Nominations Committee Meeting (Restricted), December 4, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Nominations- Alumni Trustees (Restricted), 2004 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Nominations- Directors at Large (Restricted), 2004 (Box 19, Folder 4-5)
    - Nominations (Restricted), 2004 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Nominations Committee Meeting (Restricted), January 29, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Nominations Committee Meeting (Restricted), April 1, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Nominations- Directors at Large (Restricted), 2005 (Box 19, Folder 9-10)
    - Nominations- Regional Directors (Restricted), 2005 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Nominations Committee Meeting (Restricted), January 27, 2006 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Nominations (Restricted), 2006 (Box 19, Folder 13-15)
    - Board of Trustees Selection Process (Restricted) (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Alumni Trustees Nominations Process (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Institutional Advancement, 6.
    - Institutional Advancement Office (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Institutional Advancement Handbook (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Institutional Advancement Goals & Objectives, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Institutional Advancement Plans, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Institutional Advancement Development Report, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Institutional Advancement Three-Year Progress Report, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Institutional Advancement Accountability Report, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Institutional Advancement Committee Meetings, 1999-2003 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Institutional Advancement Staff Meeting, May 10, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Institutional Advancement Staff Meeting, September 9, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Institutional Advancement Information Meeting, June 24, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - Institutional Advancement Information Meeting, June 23, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - Institutional Advancement Third Quarter Review, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Institutional Advancement Quarterly Planning, January 13, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Institutional Advancement Third Quarter Review Meeting, April 7, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Institutional Advancement First Quarter Review Meeting, October 11, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Institutional Advancement Second Quarter Review Meeting, January 20, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Presentation to Institutional Advancement Committee- Eva Bloom, June 24, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Institutional Advancement Senior Staff Retreat, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Institutional Advancement Senior Staff Retreat, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Institutional Advancement Senior Staff Retreat, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Institutional Advancement Summer Picnic, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Alumni Association Payment for Institutional Advancement Expenses, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - General Correspondence Files, 7.
    - Chronology Files, July 1, 2002 - September 30, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Chronology Files, October 3, 2002 - December 20, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Chronology Files, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 14-15)
    - Chronology Files, January 8, 2003 - May 7, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Chronology Files, May 8, 2003-June 30, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Chronology Files, July 1, 2003 - September 17, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Chronology Files, October 2, 2003 - December 18, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Chronology Files, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Chronology Files, January 6, 2004 - April 15, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Chronology Files, April 28, 2004 - June 24, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Chronology Files, July, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Chronology Files, August, 2004 - October, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Chronology Files, November, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Chronology Files, December, 2004 - January, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Chronology Files, February, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Chronology Files, March, 2005 - April, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Chronology Files, May, 2005 - June, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - Chronology Files, July 1, 2005 - June 30, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 31)
- Finances, 1992-2006; III.
  This series contains records pertaining to the finances of the Alumni Association. It includes information on fundraising and the Association's financial reports, such as business expenses, budgets, and financial records.
  - Fundraising, 1.
    - Donation Call Reports, 1992-1997 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - An Evening with the Coaches, May 31, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - An Evening with the Coaches, May 1, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Murder Mystery Fundraiser, March 3, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Murder Mystery Fundraiser Correspondence, March 3, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Murder Mystery Fundraiser, September 20, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Murder Mystery Fundraiser Correspondence, September 20, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Monte Carlo Night, May 16, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Monte Carlo Night, October 1, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Financial Reports, 2.
    - Travel & Business Expense Reports, 2000-2003 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Travel & Business Expense Reports, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Travel & Business Expense Reports, 2005 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Fiscal Reports, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Fiscal Reports, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Fiscal Reports, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Fiscal Reports, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Fiscal Reports, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Fiscal Reports, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Fiscal Reports, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Direct Reports, 2005 (Box 21, Folder 19-20)
    - Budget Planning, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Budget Planning, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 22-23)
    - Financial Records, July, 2005 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Financial Records, August, 2005 (Box 22, Folder 2-3)
    - Financial Records, September, 2005 (Box 22, Folder 4-5)
    - Financial Records, October, 2005 (Box 22, Folder 6-7)
    - Financial Records, November, 2005 (Box 22, Folder 8-9)
    - Financial Records, December, 2005 (Box 22, Folder 10-11)
    - Financial Records, January, 2006 (Box 22, Folder 12-13)
    - Financial Records, February, 2006 (Box 22, Folder 14-15)
    - Financial Records, March, 2006 (Box 22, Folder 16-17)
    - Financial Records, April, 2006 (Box 23, Folder 1-2)
    - Financial Records, May, 2006 (Box 23, Folder 3-4)
    - Financial Records, June, 2006 (Box 23, Folder 5-6)
- Constituent Groups, 1991-2006; IV.
  This series details records pertaining to the various groups associated with the Alumni Association. This includes a variety of outside groups and companies and the Crohn's & Colitis Foundation of America, as well as University of Pittsburgh groups, such as the African American Alumni Council, the Alumnae Council, the Pitt Alumni Recruitment Team, and other university constituent groups.
  - Outside Groups & Companies, 1.
    - ADVANCE (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Bell Atlantic Mobile (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Computing Services and Systems Development (CSSD) (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Danbury Mint (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Eberly Foundation (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - eTrieve (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - First USA Bank, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Giving USA (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Grenzebach, Glier, and Associates, Inc., 1996 (Box 23, Folder 15-17)
    - Ketchum Communications (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Leadership Pittsburgh (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Performance Enhancement Group, Ltd. (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Performance Now (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Placement and Career Services (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Reeher Group (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Sprint (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Verizon (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Westmoreland Management Group (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - African American Alumni Council, 2.
    - Blue, Gold and Black Magazine, 2004, undated (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Blue, Gold and Black Magazine, 2006 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - AAAC Newsletter, January, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - AAAC Newsletter, Fall 1998 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - AAAC Newsletter, November, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Chancellor's Reception, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - African American Pitt Club, 1991-1992 (Box 24, Folder 7-8)
    - AAAC Elections, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - AAAC Nominations, 1994, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - AAAC Meetings, 1992-1993 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - AAAC Meeting, May 3, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - AAAC Reunion Committee, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Alleghenians Ltd., Inc., 10th Annual Celebration Evening of Recognition- Rev. J.A. Williams Award Dinner, February 24, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - AAAC Prominent Alumni (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - AAAC (Box 24, Folder 16-18)
  - Alumnae Council, 3.
    - Alumnae Council, 1993-1995 (Box 24, Folder 19-21)
    - Alumnae Council Event Programs (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Children's Holiday Party, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Children's Holiday Party, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Children's Holiday Party, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Children's Holiday Party, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Children's Holiday Party, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Spring Luncheon, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Spring Luncheon, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Spring Event, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Spring Event, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Spring Event, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Silent Auction, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Lantern Night, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Lantern Night, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Lantern Night, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Lantern Night, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Lantern Night, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Lantern Night, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Lantern Night, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Lantern Night, 2005 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Lantern Night, 2006 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Lantern Night, 2007 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Crohn's & Colitis Foundation of America, 4.
    - CCFA (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - CCFA Correspondence (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - CCFA Financial Information (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - CCFA Fundraising (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - CCFA Publicity (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Pitt Alumni Recruitment Team, 5.
    - Pitt Alumni Recruitment Team (PART) (Box 25, Folder 22-24)
    - PART Travel- Bruce Neimeyer (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - University Constituent Groups, 6.
    - Alumni Relations Five-Year Plan, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Alumni Relations Staff Meetings, 2000-2001 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Alumni Relations Staff Meetings, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Alumni Relations Staff Retreat, July 7, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Blue and Gold Society (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Greek Alumni Council (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Pitt Ambassadors (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Varsity Letter Club (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - New York Pitt Clubs (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Student Alumni Association, April - June, 2006 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Pitt Stock of the Month Club (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Enrollment Management Committee (Box 26, Folder 12-13)
- Alumni Networking, 1986-2001; V.
  This series contains records relating to how alumni can stay in touch or be contacted. This includes the Alumni Online Community and Alumni Directory initiatives, as well as several copies of the Alumni Directory.
  - Alumni Online Community, 1.
    - Communications Plan, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Communications Plan Meetings, 1993-1994 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Harris Internet Services (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Harris Career Module (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Harris Advisory Council (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Online Community (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Online Community Correspondence (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Online Community Steering Committee (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Online Community Ad-Hoc Committee (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Online Community Ad-Hoc Committee Correspondence (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Online Task Force (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Online Task Force Correspondence (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Email Policy (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Alumni Directory, 2.
    - Alumni Directory- Harris Company (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Alumni Directory- Harris Company Correspondence (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Alumni Directory- Proposal (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Alumni Directory- Pre-contract (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Alumni Directory- Pre-contract Correspondence (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Alumni Directory- Contract (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Alumni Directory- Drafts (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Alumni Directory- Sample Cover (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Alumni Directory- Guide to Data Exchange (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Alumni Directory- How to Prepare Editorial Section (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Alumni Directory- Editorial Section (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Alumni Directory- Editorial Section Original Materials (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Alumni Directory- Editorial Section Proofs (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Alumni Directory- Issues (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Alumni Directory- Complaints for Removal (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Alumni Directory- Pitt Law School, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Alumni Directory- Pitt Bradford Campus, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Alumni Directory, 1990-1991 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Alumni Directory, 2001 (Box 27, Folder 20)
- Events, 1986-2007; VI.
  This series documents the events and activities sponsored by or attended by members of the Alumni Association. The Alumni Association has held events related to Homecoming and basketball and football games, as well as hosting dinners and receptions and presenting awards. They have also held lecture series and similar events such as University on the Road and the Chancellor's Tour in order to promote the university. Events such as Pittnics, Pitt Day, Discovery Weekend, and the Summer Discovery Showcase have all helped to promote the university as well. Constituent groups like the African American Alumni Council have held their own events, and there have been memorial events and a variety of other events for Alumni Association members.
  - Alumni Leaders Conference (ALC), 1.
    - Alumni Leaders Conference, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Alumni Leaders Conference, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 2-5)
    - Alumni Leaders Conference, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 6-8)
    - Alumni Leaders Conference, 1999 (Box 28, Folder 9-13)
    - Alumni Leaders Conference Panels, Focus Groups, Keynote Speeches, 1999 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Alumni Leaders Conference, 2002 (Box 28, Folder 15-17)
    - Alumni Leaders Conference, 2004 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Homecoming, 2.
    - Reunion Weekend, April 27, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Reunion Weekend, April 24-26, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Reunion Weekend, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Alumni Reunion Guestbook, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Reunion Weekend, 1995 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Reunion Weekend, 1997 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Reunion Weekend, October 16-17, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 7-9)
    - Homecoming, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Homecoming, 1995 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Homecoming, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Homecoming, 1997 (Box 29, Folder 13-14)
    - Homecoming, 1998 (Folder 15-24, Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Homecoming, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 2-7)
    - Homecoming, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 8-9)
    - Homecoming, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 10-14)
    - Homecoming, 2002 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Homecoming, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Homecoming, 2005 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Homecoming Sponsors
      - Baierl Auto, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 18)
      - Bowser Pontiac, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 19)
      - Chancellor Media, Inc., 1998 (Box 29, Folder 20)
      - Chujko Brothers, Inc., 1998 (Box 29, Folder 21)
      - Gateway Outdoor Advertising, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 22)
      - Hampton Inn, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 23)
      - Holiday Inn, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 24)
      - Howard Hanna, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 25)
      - KQV 1410AM, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 26-27)
      - Paws, Inc., 1998 (Box 29, Folder 28)
      - Pepsi, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 29)
      - Sargent Electric, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 30)
      - Stuckert's Exxon, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 31)
      - Transportation Displays, Inc., 1998 (Box 29, Folder 32)
      - Tribune-Review, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 33)
      - University Club, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 34)
      - US Airways, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 35)
      - Wyndham, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 36)
  - African American Alumni Council, 3.
    - AAAC Homecoming, October 21, 1995 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - AAAC Homecoming, October 4-5, 1996 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - AAAC Reunion, 1997 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - AAAC Homecoming, September 19, 1997 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - AAAC Homecoming, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 5-8)
    - AAAC Homecoming, 1999 (Box 31, Folder 9-11)
    - AAAC Homecoming, 2000 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - AAAC Homecoming, 2001 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - AAAC Homecoming, 2003 (Box 31, Folder 14-16)
    - AAAC Homecoming, 2006 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - AAAC Psychology Reunion, July 12, 2003 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - AAAC PART, 1999 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - AAAC Fundraiser- Atlanta, February 26, 2000 (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - AAAC Fundraiser- Philadelphia, June 10, 2000 (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - AAAC Events, 1997-1998 (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - AAAC Events (Box 31, Folder 23-26)
  - Basketball, 4.
    - Basketball Correspondence (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Basketball Season, 2002-2003 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Basketball Tickets- Alumni Group Seating, 2002-2003 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Big East Tournament, March 11-16, 2003 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - NCAA Tournament, March 21-23, 2003 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - NCAA Tournament- Sweet Sixteen, March 27-30, 2003 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Pitt vs. Chicago State, December 17, 2003 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Pitt vs. Syracuse, February 29, 2004 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - NCAA Tournament, March 19-22, 2004 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - NCAA Tournament- Sweet Sixteen, March 25-28, 2004 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Basketball Awards Banquet, April 13, 2004 (Box 32, Folder 11)